(Leonard:)She likes everybody
better than she likes me!
(Raj:)How old is this Jell-O?
(Stuart:)Well, it's carrots,
so gonna say very.
(Howard:)Sorry we have to do this.
(Stuart:)Bernadette's not wrong.
(Stuart:)She does work hard around here.
(Raj:)Yeah, maybe it's a good thing
(Raj:)if she stops
babying you so much.
(Howard:)She doesn't baby me.
(Stuart:)I saw her pull you home
in a wagon.
(Howard:)For your information,
(Howard:)I twisted my ankle
chasing the ice cream truck.
(Raj:)Face it, dude, Bernadette
treats you the same way
(Raj:)your mother used to, and that
was not a healthy relationship.
(Leonard:)You're right.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)It's time for me
(Howard:)to act like an adult
in this marriage.
(Howard:)Starting with my husbandly duty
of taking out the trash.